// Civics Questions
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What does democracy mean?",
    answer: "Equal right to vote",
    options: [
      "Maps",
      "Equal right to vote",
      "Caricatures",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "According to Universal Adult Franchise every adult has:",
    answer: "one vote",
    options: [
      "multiple vote",
      "one vote",
      "No vote",
      "All of these"

    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is NOT the element of equality?",
    answer: " Religion",
    options: [
      "Justice",
      "Religion",
      "Wealth",
      "Health"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Whose autobiography is ‘Joothan’?",
    answer: "Omprakash Valmiki’s",
    options: [
      "Atal Bihari Vajpayee’s",
      "Omprakash Valmiki’s",
      "Mahatma Gandhi’s",
      "Pt. Jawaharlal Nehru’s"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "When persons are treated unequally what is violated?",
    answer: "Dignity",
    options: [
      "Religion",
      "Caste",
      "Dignity",
      "Practice"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 6,
  question: "The Indian constitution recognises",
  answer: "all people are equal",
  options: [
    "all people are not equal",
    "all people are equal",
    "all people are economically sound",
    "none of these"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 7,
  question: "Who drafted the Indian Constitution?",
  answer: "Dr. B.R. Ambedkar",
  options: [
    "Pt. J.L. Nehru",
    "Dr. B.R. Ambedkar",
    "Mahatma Gandhi",
    "Lai Bahadur Shastri"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 8,
  question: "Who represent our problems in the Parliament House?",
  answer: "MPs",
  options: [
    "Ourselves",
    "MPs",
    "MLAs",
    "SHO"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 9,
  question: "Civil Rights movement of USA was about:",
  answer: "Afro Americans",
  options: [
    "Indo Americans",
    "Afro Americans",
    "Both of these",
    "None of these"
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 10,
  question: "What is the central feature of Democracy?",
  answer: "Equality",
  options: [
    "Equality",
    "Inequality",
    "Discrimination",
    "restrictions"
  ]
},

];
